<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>relationships on PhantomBroken</title>
    <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/relationships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in relationships on PhantomBroken</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/relationships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Going through the Dark Night of The Soul. Why is this Happening?</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/darknightofthesoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/darknightofthesoul/</guid>
      <description>Going through the Dark Night of the Soul, can sometimes feel pretty scary&amp;hellip; the way that we&amp;rsquo;ve perceived life is crumbling before our eyes. Everything from what we believed is to be to being revealed what the truth is either in our personal lives or looking what society is. All of these multiple factors were the reason why the Dark Night of the Soul happened to me. But why does this happen in the first place anyways?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Stars (Epilogue)</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/lovestarpoem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 11:18:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/lovestarpoem/</guid>
      <description>here we are my scars turned into actual Love Stars this time, it isn&amp;rsquo;t love that is unrequited but it&amp;rsquo;s very alive and excited like a hero in the night skyscraper I want to take that leap of faith and become greater maybe soulmates aren&amp;rsquo;t found but are created it was worth the pain and the waiting I know we&amp;rsquo;re scared you&amp;rsquo;ve promised that you&amp;rsquo;ll never hurt me and never abandon or flee as I promised that I&amp;rsquo;ll still love you even if we get old long distance as of this moment but I still wanna wrap my arms around you and hold we maybe physically far but so energetically close time don&amp;rsquo;t exist when I talk to you the clocks become completely froze a new story is about to be told I&amp;rsquo;m sorry that you were cheated as my previous attempts of love were untreated as everything happens for a reason, canon events, makes us grow and ascend as you are my Mary Jane and Gwen at the same time but you are yourself which I love the most I know we&amp;rsquo;re not perfect but no one is your the reason why I keep pushing and why life is so beautiful to live I see why now this love is so unbound</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reunited</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/reunited/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/reunited/</guid>
      <description>this tension is building up inside of me
to the point where I don’t know how to explain it within me
something about us sparked a flame that I would never forget
too bad we never commit, I think deep down is what we regret
I just wanna hug you tight
fight for you right by your side
close off the outside world
as we run in the beautiful night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving Foward, Heartbreak and healing</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/movingforward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/movingforward/</guid>
      <description>I keep running away from the things that I need to face, being attached on with the past and I can&amp;rsquo;t run and hide forever. Made a lot of mistakes with that connection that could&amp;rsquo;ve been something but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t mean&amp;rsquo;t to be. I&amp;rsquo;m still learning on how to move forward from it, which is still a challenge for me, reminsing about the times I had with her, mourning on what I lost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
