<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shadow Work on PhantomBroken</title>
    <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/shadow-work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shadow Work on PhantomBroken</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/shadow-work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Going through the Dark Night of The Soul. Why is this Happening?</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/darknightofthesoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/darknightofthesoul/</guid>
      <description>Going through the Dark Night of the Soul, can sometimes feel pretty scary&amp;hellip; the way that we&amp;rsquo;ve perceived life is crumbling before our eyes. Everything from what we believed is to be to being revealed what the truth is either in our personal lives or looking what society is. All of these multiple factors were the reason why the Dark Night of the Soul happened to me. But why does this happen in the first place anyways?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing The Brainwashing</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/removingthebrainwashing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/removingthebrainwashing/</guid>
      <description>From when we were born, we were taught things that were false and many lies that I still see people believing, and even myself.
What I&amp;rsquo;m talking about most importantly in this post, which we will focus on and the most thing that many people seem to struggle and get the wrong idea about on how to be free from this trap with the many fear and psychological traps of today day in age of shoving sexual media in our faces and porn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Hip-Hop became my Therapy</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/hiphopthreapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/hiphopthreapy/</guid>
      <description>About two years ago, I was in a separation with this girl that I liked, which was sadly cut off too shortly after major agendas were taking place around the world. A lot of grief, mourning, heartbreak took place with a lot elephants in the room needing to be addressed between me and her, as I tried to reach out to her, though she became very distant, closed off and avoided me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving Foward, Heartbreak and healing</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/movingforward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/movingforward/</guid>
      <description>I keep running away from the things that I need to face, being attached on with the past and I can&amp;rsquo;t run and hide forever. Made a lot of mistakes with that connection that could&amp;rsquo;ve been something but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t mean&amp;rsquo;t to be. I&amp;rsquo;m still learning on how to move forward from it, which is still a challenge for me, reminsing about the times I had with her, mourning on what I lost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
