<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medium Archives on PhantomBroken</title>
    <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/medium-archives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Medium Archives on PhantomBroken</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/medium-archives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Hip-Hop became my Therapy</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/hiphopthreapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/hiphopthreapy/</guid>
      <description>About two years ago, I was in a separation with this girl that I liked, which was sadly cut off too shortly after major agendas were taking place around the world. A lot of grief, mourning, heartbreak took place with a lot elephants in the room needing to be addressed between me and her, as I tried to reach out to her, though she became very distant, closed off and avoided me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flipping the Script (Cobra Kai Philosophy)</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/cobrakai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/cobrakai/</guid>
      <description>This show signal handily helped me so much when going through life. Throughout this show, we see Eli who was an introvert, hated himself, and was constantly bullied by his appearance with his cleft lip until he took the tough love advice from Johnny Lawrence and grabbed life by the balls and turning the tables that he has the power, while not waiting for anyone to make a change for himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Always Have a Choice</title>
      <link>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/uncleben/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterparkercode.github.io/posts/uncleben/</guid>
      <description>“With great power, there must also come — great responsibility.” No matter what in life, we always have a choice to make the right decisions, even if it feels like we’re forced to do said things that doesn’t resonate with us and know that is not the best option. We have the choice to not only to make the right decisions for ourselves, but for others and for the sake of the betterment of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
